[Episode 13]
Then go back to Australia.
If it's that pretty, go to your country
and live happily.
How would it feel to be up there?
Would it look much better than it does from here?
If you're so curious, then why don't you go?
I am going.
I'll be going there soon.
You and I weren't meant to be this time around.
Let's meet in the next life.
The Rose of Sharon is in bloom.
Uncle! You moved!
You're it!
Ready?
The Rose of Sharon is in bloom!
The Rose of Sharon is in...
Bloomed!
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Eunchae?
What happened?
What is it?
Eunchae! What happened? Huh?
Eunchae!
Eunchae! Eunchae!
Are you okay?
Let's put some medicine on it.
Let's go inside and rub some medicine on it.
Are you hurt anywhere else?
You should be more careful, dummy!
Let go.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Eunchae.
I said I'm fine!
I don't feel a thing!
This is nothing. It doesn't hurt.
I'm fine.
Eunchae got hurt.
She looks like she's hurting. A lot.
What should we do? What should we do?
Eunchae.
Why didn't you tell me Muhyeok was sick?
Because you thought I might leave Yun?
Were you afraid I'd go to Muhyeok?
Is that why you didn't tell me?
Did Yun's mother tell you to hide it from me?
Let's go inside. Let's go home.
You should have told me.
Do you know what I did to Muhyeok?
Do you know what I said?
What's wrong with your face? Did you get hurt?
You should have told me sooner!
Dad, I was so harsh to him.
Do you know how cruel I was to him?
Let's go inside.
I'm going to go to Yun.
I'm going to go and tell him
to let me go to Muhyeok at least now.
I'm going to go tell Yun!
Eunchae!
I'm going to tell him to let me go to Muhyeok.
I'll beg him to let me go.
- Go inside.
- Dad!
- Eunchae!
- Dad, please let me go!
- Dad!
- Let me go!
- Get inside!
Why isn't Eunchae home yet?
She's been out forever to get the tofu.
That's what I'm saying.
Maybe she's gone to the bean field
to make the tofu herself.
You don't think someone
put her in his pocket and took her away
because she's so tiny and cute, do you?
That's what I'm...
not saying!
Mom, you think too highly of your child.
Eunchae is cute, but she's not that cute.
But me, well...
I'm so worried. Sukchae, go and find Eunchae.
Hey. You go.
She told you to go.
I don't want to. It's cold.
I ought to just...
How are you always so violent?
Disgusting, disgusting.
I feel bad for Eunchae who
has to call you two her siblings!
You brats wouldn't even blink an eye if Eunchae died!
What am I going to do with you two?
- Get inside!
- Let go!
- Dad, please just let go!
- Get inside!
- What are you doing?
Dad!
I don't want you to take one step out of this room!
Dad.
I'm not going to let you go to Yun or Muhyeok!
Dad!
Don't answer your phone.
Open the door!
Honey, what's gotten into you?
If anyone of you opens this door,
I won't let you get away with it.
It looked like Eunchae was hurt.
She was limping and had scratches.
Don't you think we should at least
give her some ointment?
- Sukchae! Minchae!
- Yes?
You two sleep in our room,
and I'll sleep in the living room.
Uh. Dad, my wallet and clothes are in there.
I have a job interview tomorrow.
Don't go!
My bag's in there.
I have homework to do and school tomorrow.
Don't go to your interview, and don't go to school!
How will she eat?
We can't starve her like some criminal.
Let her starve.
Are you out of your mind?
What if my Eunchae dies?
Are you about to kill our Eunchae?
She won't die! Don't worry!
Start packing. We're moving.
Move? Where? Why?
Anywhere! Transfer Minchae to a different school!
Dad, you can't do this on short...
I'm going to look for a house we
can move into immediately, so pack your bags!
I'm warning you again.
If any one of you opens the door for Eunchae...
I'll divorce you, and I'll disown you kids!
If you want to test me, do it!
If you get a call from Yun,
tell him Eunchae went away and that
you don't know when she'll be back.
Mom, is that person really our father?
What's gotten into him? Was he struck by lightning?
Maybe he did get hit by lightning.
It feels like I've been hit by lightning just now!
Oh, dear. Eunchae. Eunchae.
Eunchae, just wait a little.
I'll open the door for you.
Minchae, hammer! Get the hammer!
Mom, do you want to get a divorce?
You know dad is a man of his word.
Are you prepared for the consequences?
Eunchae, are you okay?
You seemed hurt. Are you okay?
What should we do? I can't even put medicine on it.
Where and how much does it hurt? Huh?
Eunchae!
You didn't even eat yet. I'm sure you're hungry...
What did you do to deserve such punishment?
What did you do to make Dad so angry?
Why are you here?
I'm here to see Eunchae.
I sent Eunchae to the country.
She's not home. You should go.
Please let me see her.
- I said she's not home.
- Please let me see her.
Go home.
What are you talking about?
Where did Eunchae go?
The countryside? Why all of a sudden?
You don't know when she'll be back?
Mr. Song... What...
Wait a second.
I know you're mad at me, but you
shouldn't take it out on my sick boy Yun.
You know Yun can't live without Eunchae!
You know that very well,
so don't be so immature about it
and send Eunchae over.
Mr. Song. Mr. Song!
[Song Eunchae]
Your call has been forwarded to an...
Eunchae, not you, too.
I guess I'll just go to Yeonsu's
and borrow her books for homework.
Why don't you wear Mom's clothes to your interview?
We'll be fine, one way or another,
but what about Eunchae being
locked up in our room like that?
How will she go to the bathroom?
Well, she hasn't eaten,
so maybe she won't need to go.
I think Dad's really set on killing Eunchae.
You don't think he's really going to kill her, do you?
Eunchae's locked up?
- No.
- Yes.
No! Eunchae's not home! She went to the country.
No! You can't!
She'll die, my mom's marriage will end up in a divorce,
and we will lose our father!
Please spare us!
Eunchae went to the country.
Something important came up.
She'll be back in a couple of days.
She'll be back soon.
Should I go home and check?
I can ask exactly where she is and
exactly when she's coming back.
Yeah, I'll do that.
Mom. Don't go.
Don't go, just stay here.
She'll be back when she's ready to come back.
I think it's raining outside.
You like it when it rains.
Did you finish your homework?
Did you borrow clothes?
You're still here?
Let me see Eunchae.
You can't. It'll break our family apart if you do.
Eunchae, are you all right?
When your father comes, I'll open
the door and give you some food.
Your father's not cruel enough
to kill his own daughter.
He just did this to scare you.
Wait a little longer. Just a little, okay?
What do we do, Mom?
Why?
Yun's manager is out front.
What?
My heart's being ripped to shreds!
It's freezing outside. And raining.
Open the door. Please.
Please, open the door!
Sukchae, Minchae, Mom.
Please, please.
I'll just send him home, and I'll be right back.
He shouldn't be out like that.
He'll die if he's out there like that.
Please...
Mom, I think Eunchae's hitting
her head against the door.
What do we do? What do we do?
What's wrong with her now? Eunchae! Don't!
Don't hit your head. Eunchae.
Stop it! Don't, Eunchae!
Did you put on some medicine?
Did you put medicine on your forehead
where you got hurt?
I knew it.
So I got some medicine for my Blockhead.
It might hurt a little. You can handle it.
It stings, huh?
No.
My Blockhead. You're so ugly.
Skinned forehead. Face full of bruises.
You're so ugly I can't look at you.
I won't look. You're too ugly!
Smile. Just like that.
You're tolerable to look at when you smile.
Actually, you look pretty.
Not as pretty as the Miss Australia I used to date,
but you look better than Shrek.
Fine! We'll get a divorce! Let's get one!
I'd rather get a divorce than see my daughter suffer.
It's not Mom's fault. You can disown me.
I broke the lock with my hammer.
You didn't break it on your own. Dad, I helped.
You can disown me, too.
What is it? What is it?
Why are you acting as if you got struck by lightning?
And why was Yun's manager waiting
in the rain to see Eunchae?
And why was Eunchae banging her
head on the door to see him?
Tell me! I'm Eunchae's mother!
I need to know what's going on with my daughter.
I want to know!
What on earth happened to Eunchae?
Eunchae.
My goodness...
The motel manager's so nice.
He gave us a line to hang clothes,
an iron, and let you borrow his pants.
He's going to be blessed.
I was Yun stylist for five years,
so I know a thing or two about wet clothes.
I could get a doctorate in drying
if there was such a thing.
Here, put it on.
Are you scared?
Are you scared about hearing my story?
Is that why you're only showing me your back?
No.
I got shot at my wife's wedding.
The bullet was lodged in a place
too dangerous to remove.
The bullet is right here.
Scary, huh?
Good. It's nothing to be afraid of.
It's the same with death. It's not scary.
It's a normal part of life. Everyone dies.
It shouldn't be something
to get serious about or feel pity over.
Wait. Saying that doesn't do me any good.
I take it back. I take back everything I just said.
I'm really sad. I'm very sad.
You'll never find someone with a sadder story.
I have the saddest life ever.
So pity me. Don't be mean. Because I'm so pitiful...
You're not pitiful at all.
Your heart is so full of love that
you even took a bullet for a woman who betrayed you.
You have so much.
What's sad about that?
I don't pity you.
I've never looked at you with pity.
And I never will.
Does it hurt a lot?
Are you okay?
Open the door. Let me in.
Let me in, Mister.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Please, open the door.
I'll go in.
It's embarrassing. You can't.
I'll be out in a second.
I'll be out soon.
Eunchae, go home.
Go home. What if your family
falls apart because of this?
Go home.
Let me just see your face first.
Go, Eunchae.
I'll go after I see your face.
No.
I'm so ugly that I don't want you to see me!
Go.
Mister.
If I go, it'll be hard for me to come back.
I can't just ignore Yun.
I can't.
I can't go and leave Yun now.
I made Yun like that.
I put a nail in Yun's heart
because I want to be with you.
Because I want to take your hand.
I made Yun like that because I wanted to be with you.
I'm sorry.
There was so much I wanted to give you.
But I've only given you pain.
I have nothing to give but that.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Dad...
I know what you're worried about.
Don't make the family suffer because of me.
I'll take care of everything.
Goodnight.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry, Eunchae.
Vital signs.
Mrs. Oh, may I have a word with you?
Yun's health is not stable.
And the person who was going to
donate the heart changed his mind.
Thank you.
The presents that you sent last time...
My sister's clothes, meat, coal, fruits.
We're wearing it, using it,
and eating it very thankfully.
I'm taking the vitamins diligently, too.
And the medicine.
I'm taking the medicine that's good for the heart.
But I took some tests today and
they said my heart's so healthy
that I don't need to take them.
Uh... I made a mistake.
To tell you the truth, I was going
to give Yun that medicine.
But I accidentally brought it to your house.
The truth is, I won't be alive much longer.
I might die on the streets today.
I might not be able to wake up tomorrow morning.
If I'm lucky, I might be able to
live for three or four months.
Mr. Cha.
So today, I went to the organ donation center.
And registered to become a donor.
Yun and I are the same blood type.
Test results show Yun and I are
very compatible in all respects.
Well... Mr. Cha, what are you trying
to tell me right now?
If I die first,
I want to give my heart to Yun.
Why are you doing this, Mr. Cha?
I don't know what you heard,
but it's seriously a mistake. Mistake. Huh?
Oh, fine. I...
Because of my child, I was nuts for a while. Really.
Okay, I really was nuts.
I don't want it.
I won't take it. All right?
I don't want to. I really don't want it.
I don't want to.
The clothes that you bought for
my sister were very pretty.
Mother,
please don't cry.
What I want is not your tears.
Please, don't cry.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying? Mom?
If those tears of yours are for me...
then please don't cry.
For now on, the tears you shed
will be my tears of blood.
[Cha Muhyeok, signed donor]
Now, the best manager!
Introducing Muhyeok!
I'm Choi Yun's famous manager, Cha Muhyeok!
This is Yun, Muhyeok's eternal fan!
Are you the person who rescued us?
You don't have a brother right?
Do you want to be my brother?
I wouldn't have lived without you, right?
I wouldn't be able to eat,
wouldn't be able to go to the bathroom.
That's right!
Speaking of eating, don't mind if I have a bite myself!
Ah! Don't!
Now, the girl I'm about to introduce!
Wait a second.
Looks like she's eating something all by herself.
Like a little fool, she's laughing by herself.
- Wake up, fool!
- Blockhead!
Blockhead!
What are you doing? Stop!
How was your trip?
Yeah.
I thought it was going to take a long time.
I thought so, too,
But I came back quickly.
Uncle!
Grandpa said that he's going
to take pictures of you and me
and wants you to come outside.
What are you doing? Go sit down by your sister.
Here! Here! Here!
What are you doing?
Are you deaf?
Why do you want to take pictures all of a sudden?
I'm taking pictures because
I need to use it for something.
Go sit down.
You may not believe it, but I've
been taking pictures for years.
Just trust me.
Why are you taking the picture?
I'm going to put it in a book.
I have a book that I'm finishing up
right now. I need it to finish.
What book is it?
The book of movie star Audrey and her three children.
Do you want to take a picture?
I took individual pictures,
but I don't have a group picture. That's why.
Do you want to take it?
You don't want a picture?
I'll take it.
But can I make V signs?
Do whatever.
Muhyeok, get in closer.
Okay. One, two.
It's great.
Mother.
For now, please hold back your tears.
Your tears will become tears of blood for me.
Eunchae.
Eunchae!
Yes?
- Go home.
- What?
I want to be alone today. Go home.
Yun.
I want to listen to music.
I just want to be alone. Please.
Blockhead!
- Mister!
- Blockhead!
Enjoy.
Hey, Cha Muhyeok!
Hey.
Cha Muhyeok.
Fine, let's do it then.
Let's see how far Kang Minju will ruin herself.
How pathetic I can get.
I want to know what my limit is.
Let's do it, Cha Muhyeok!
Muhyeok.
I'd have waited ten more minutes then left.
Are you allowed to be out like this?
Nope. They probably turned the hospital
upside-down to find me.
Go back. Should I take you?
I came to say something.
I don't really want to hear anything.
I heard from my mom.
That you said you want to give me your heart.
You don't have to thank me.
That's not how it's done.
Let's go. I'll take you back.
What are you trying to get me to do?
Kill you so that I can live?
What are you doing to me?
No. I don't want it.
I'd rather die. I don't want it!
I came to say that.
Why don't you want it?
It's not like I'm dying for you.
I'm going to die regardless.
I want to do something good and end up in heaven.
Why? Are you jealous of that as well?
Then give it to someone else.
Why me?
Why does it have to be me?
Because I'm your brother.
You're my little brother, and I'm your big brother.
[Episode 14 Preview]
I told you I'd give it to you even
if you don't give me anything.
Even if you don't beg me, I've told you already
I'm going to give it to you before I die!
[Sorry, but you don't see me]
Kill you so that I can live?
[Love, but I'm in love with you]
Mother...
Mother, I'm the son you abandoned.